Hello, my friends.
And welcome to exercise number 38.
And this exercise, we are asked to write a program to shuffle and thereI, and this exercise have been
asked in one of the interviews, like in Facebook, gay and big companies like Facebook.
So how to shuffle an array?
What is shuffling?
We have the original array here one four five nine 10 shuffling make it make random random ordering
of their elements like four 10 one five nine.
If we call and if we shuffle again, we we get another random shuffling and ordering of the elements,
so we need to randomly order that elements.
OK, so post the video and think about it how to make such an algorithm or program that works well to
maintain this algorithm?
Okay, we start by making public static void shuffle.
I'm waiting.
Your solution in the comments below.
In order to discuss if there is any problem.
So this method will start by taking in an array called NUM's.
And I need from this noun to start by A.I. equal to NUM's thought length minus one I greater than or
equal to one and a minus minus gain.
We are shuffling by using the random random package as inside the Java, the two tiered the trap.
OK, so random brand equals two new random.
OK.
Int J, equal to random, I'm making random the next and I need that range of random between I plus
one, and I need to create a method called swab swab elements, and I passed the nuns by and cheer.
Let's make this method.
Swab elements.
OK, so this.
This method is private.
Avoid swab elements, it took an integrity that make swab the elements it.
It's changed the order of I and J
and start by creating an anthem.
We need a temporary variable called 10 norms at Index AI and NUM's at Index AI equal to announce at
Index J.
OK, I'm switching the elements and nuns at Index J equal to 10.
OK, I'm randomly making this so every time we start by swapping the elements.
Static here, sweeping the elements, I am making a random.
I am making it as random next and I +1 and passing the elements like the entry that I and J, and here
we start sweating.
So the temporary equal I are equal to JJ, equal to temp.
So I'm switching between the elements of I, equal to J and J, equal to.
I am swiping to be swapping the elements between I and G.
Now let's test the program and the main method I will start recreating and NUM's be equal to
the numbers.
Let me.
One, four, five, nine and 10.
OK.
System that allows the brand and original essay we use of these dogs to string.
Nuns now, after shoveling, I will start by shuffle their shuffle past nuns.
I called this method, so after the shuffling, I need to display, shuffle,
shuffled array or shuffle.
30.
OK, I have created Ray, I displayed that.
The original array, I called the method shuffle and then I will display that shuffle or let's run and
see.
And here we go.
We have one four five nine 10.
It's shuffling just one element.
OK, now let's run and see again.
One four.
It's shuffling 10, nine, five, four and maybe all the elements, all of these elements for us, if
we run again, we have another combination.
Here we are, shuffling all the elements.
It's shuffling all that, OK.
This is for making the games because if you are making card game and you are shuffling the cards.
So this is the algorithm behind shuffling that phrase.
And this is very important and it is used in many games by the.